mobilerainbow.co.uk 2004-12-04

# Privacy Policy

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you of what kinds of information we gather about you as a visitor to our website, how we may use that information and who we may share that information with. Our customer privacy policy is contained within the 'Privacy Policy' pdf. Click the link below to download this document. 

By accessing, browsing and/or using our website you agree to the following terms. If you do not agree you must cease to use our website. 

Reference to " **3** " in this Privacy Policy means Hutchison 3G UK Limited. 

• **Privacy**  
3 is committed to protecting your privacy. You may supply us with personal data at your discretion and we agree that we will deal with this data in accordance with current UK Data Protection Legislation. Please note this applies only to us and not to other companies or organisations to which we link.   
You agree that the data that you provide to us will be true, complete and accurate in all respects and you agree to notify us immediately of any changes to it. 

• **Registration**  
In order to receive certain information from us you must first complete a registration form. During registration you may be asked to provide us with your personal data. 

  * If you register as a journalist, analyst, career seeker or partner, or if you wish to register a site, this personal data will be held by us and will be used to provide you with the information you have requested. 
  * If you register to receive information about 3 products and services, this information will include your name, address, date of birth, telephone and fax numbers, gender, e-mail address, employer details, credit or debit card information, and results of credit and fraud checks. We will use this information to provide you with details of our products and services and other information you have requested in accordance with the consent you have given and, if applicable, to process any payments you wish to make to us. 

We will only keep your personal information for as long as necessary for these purposes and in accordance with our data retention policy. 

This personal data may also be processed and used by such other organisations on our behalf for the purpose of processing applications or providing information on our products and services to you. The use of personal data for these purposes will remain under our control at all times. 

We may disclose your information to other members of our group of companies, and to our or their partners, associates, agents or subcontractors and to possible successors to our business. Some of these parties may reside outside the EU. In addition, we may disclose your information to protect the interest of our other users or if required to do so by law. 

If you are aged 16 or under, please get your parent or guardian's consent to provide your personal information to 3's website, otherwise you are not allowed to provide your personal information. 

• **Cookies**  
A cookie is a small, unique text file that is saved on your hard disk by a website. The cookie is used by the website to identify your computer whenever you visit that website. We may use cookies to map usage patterns to enhance our service to you. 

• **Log files**  
We may use Usernames or IP addresses to analyse trends, administer and improve our website, track movement through our website and gather information about all our users. We may track your movements through our website, but you remain anonymous. 

• **Notification of changes**  
If we change our Privacy Policy we will post the amended Policy on our website so that you are always aware of how we collect, use and disclose your personal information. 

• **Security**  
Our database will be secured by Password protection and only authorised individuals within 3 will have the ability to access the data.   
Where you hold a Password with us please keep it safe and do not share it with others. 

• **Access to your personal information**  
You have the right to request a copy of the personal information we hold about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. We will charge an administrative fee of £10 to provide this to you. Please address requests to dpa.officer@hutchison3g.com 

• **Monitoring of phone calls/e-mails**  
By using the telephone numbers or email addresses provided on this website you are consenting to the recording or monitoring of your communication via those access devices. 

**Other terms and conditions**  
You are also subject to our General Terms and Conditions
